digyourowngrave.com 2010-12-29

# The Littlegrey Network – Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

The following Privacy Policy covers all of the Littlegrey Network Websites, specifically [**The Littlegrey Network**](http://www.littlegrey.net/) (www.littlegrey.net), [**Dig Your Own Grave**](http://www.digyourowngrave.com/) (www.digyourowngrave.com), and [**Video Fantastica**](http://www.videofantastica.com/) (www.videofantastica.com). Please read this statement carefully. If you do not agree to these terms and conditions, do not use this, or any other Littlegrey Network Website.

### Ownership of Information

Littlegrey Media is the sole owner of the information collected on the Littlegrey Network Websites.

### Personal Information

Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you with a friendly, customized, and efficient experience. We only collect personal information that is relevant to the purpose of our websites. We do not process this information in a way that is incompatible with the purpose for which it has been collected or subsequently authorized by you. We receive and store any information you enter on our website or provide to us in any other way. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features. The personal information you provide is used for such purposes as registration. In order for you to use Littlegrey Network services, such as commenting, and submitting links, you must complete a registration form. As part of this registration form, we require your email address.

If you feel any of your personal information is publicly posted in error, contact us at [support@littlegrey.net](mailto:support@littlegrey.net) to have the information removed.

### Third Party Advertising and Cookies

The ads appearing on Littlegrey Network Websites are delivered to users by third party advertisers. These companies may use information about your visits to this and other Websites in order to provide advertisements on the Littlegrey Network sites and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. These advertisers may use cookies on our sites to accomplish this. However, Littlegrey Media has no access to, or control over, these cookies once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Littlegrey Media only, and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

Google Adsense ads featured across the Littlegrey Network Websites make use of the [DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx). Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads based on your visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

### Log Files

Like most standard Website servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, number of clicks, etc. to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. None of this data is linked to personally identifiable information.

### Sharing Information

Except as expressly set forth herein, Littlegrey Media will never loan, give away, sell, distribute or rent your personal information to any third party. Furthermore, Littlegrey Media does not divulge any information regarding the users who use email for correspondence with the webmaster or any representative of Littlegrey Media.

### Legal Disclaimer

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, Littlegrey Media may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order, or legal process served on any of the Littlegrey Network Websites.

### Business Transitions

In the event that Littlegrey Media goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of a portion of its assets, users' personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.

### Links

The Littlegrey Network Websites contain links to other sites. Please be aware that Littlegrey Media is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave any of our sites and to read the Privacy Policies of each and every Website that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by Littlegrey Media.

### Notification of Changes

We reserve the right to change or modify our privacy practices that are described herein simply by posting a revised Privacy Policy on this Website. Any such change shall be effective immediately upon posting of the revised Privacy Policy on this Website. We reserve the right to make the revised or changed Privacy Policy effective for information we already have about you, as well as any information we receive in the future. We encourage you to refer to this Privacy Policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current privacy practices.

### Contact Information

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, the practices of any Littlegrey Network Website, or your dealings with any Littlegrey Media Website, please contact us at [support@littlegrey.net](mailto:support@littlegrey.net).
